protoshare.com 2018-11-20

# Privacy Policy | ProtoShare

Site9 respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of all personal data shared with Site9. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request, to collect payment for those services, or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

##### Information Collection

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, physical address, and other information when needed to provide a service you requested. We may also collect billing information such as a credit card number to facilitate payment for our services.

When you visit this site and engage in certain activities, Site9 may request certain personally identifying information about you. For example, when you request information about Site9 services, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself such as your name, address and company information. Site9 may use this information to respond to your request, and to keep you informed about existing or new service availability or improvements, special offers, and other information about Site9 services.

If you already are a customer of Site9 ("Customer"), you may request access to your account and information related thereto. As part of the process of giving you access to your account, we may request information that identifies you as a customer, such as your password and/or login information. Site9 encrypts all such customer-identifying information provided to us. We recommend that you not divulge your password to anyone, since you are responsible for any activities undertaken through use of your password access, whether by you or by someone else.

Site9 sends personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people: 1) when we have your consent to share the information; 2) when we need to share your information with third parties, such as banks and credit card processors, to provide the product or service you have requested; 3) in connection with products and services offered by Site9 but provided by a third party on our behalf; 4) it is appropriate or necessary to comply with law; 5) it is necessary to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our agreements; or 6) it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of Site9, our users, or others, which may include the exchange of information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

In the event that Site9 is acquired (by sale of stock, sale of assets or otherwise), your account information may be one of the transferred assets.

##### Third Party Sites

Your customer information and the substance of your request may also be provided to trusted third parties in order to register or fulfill your order, or to confirm your right, if any, to technical support, services or other benefits that may be made available to you and your company. Site9 may monitor and aggregate visitor traffic pattern data, and may use and disclose such aggregate information to third parties to help resolve matters regarding your web site and for other business reasons agreed to by you in advance. This aggregated information does not personally identify you.

Site9's ProtoShare.com may contain links to web sites operated by other companies. Although we choose our business partners carefully, Site9 is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. Once you have left our web site, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party web site to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

##### Cookies and Site9

A cookie is a small data file that we write to your hard drive when you visit ProtoShare.com. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that our site uses to track the pages you've visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by

other sites. Some cookies track user traffic patterns. We use cookies in order to determine the usefulness of information to you and our other users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. Site9 does not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor does it share this information or sell it to any third party.

If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. Please note, however, that some areas of ProtoShare.com will not be accessible if you do not have cookies turned on.

Site9 has no control over any cookies you may receive from visiting websites of any third parties or advertisers, and therefore Site9 has no control over your ability to accept or reject their cookies should you choose to interact with such third parties or advertisers.

##### Security/Encryption

Site9 protects your privacy. All communication between the web browser and our servers is encrypted. All Site9 servers have their own firewalls to protect your data. These firewalls are continually tested to ensure your security. Site9 stores credit card information only for the purpose of satisfying your monthly recurring obligation to Site9, if any.

Site9 employees do not have direct access to your password because all passwords are encrypted in our database. The original password cannot be accessed even outside the system as passwords are never transmitted in plain text. Should you forget your password, please contact us and we can help you to reset your account and choose a new password.

##### Credit Card Payments

Site9 offers you the option of paying your monthly recurring fees using a credit card. All cardholder information entered on the ProtoShare.com website is encrypted for your protection. We collect cardholder information solely for the purpose of processing your payments. Such information is used only by Site9 personnel directly involved in the processing of your transactions.

##### Google User Data

While using the ProtoShare Mockups for Drive application, Google user data may be accessed and used for the sole purpose of application functionality. This includes the currently logged in Google user's email address, ProtoShare Mockups for Drive application settings and saved mockup files. No Google user data is stored outside of Google Drive or shared with third party sites.

##### Changes to This Policy

Site9 will amend this policy from time to time. Please note that any modifications and amendments to this policy may be made at any time, and will be effective immediately. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. An updated version of the terms of use will always be available for you to review on line at [protoshare.com/privacy](http://protoshare.com/privacy). Checking the privacy policy periodically will keep you apprised of any and all modifications made.

##### Dispute Resolution Mechanism

Site9 is committed to resolving our customers' privacy concerns. Individuals should work directly with their assigned Account Manager to address concerns arising from Site9's use of private information. If unable to address the issue via the assigned account team, individuals should contact Site9 directly via e-mail at [privacy@site9.com](mailto:privacy@site9.com) stating the suspected misuse of information.

##### US-EU Safe Harbor Framework

Site9, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Site9, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Site9, Inc.'s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

##### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at the email address above.

If you have any question or concerns about what has been stated in this Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us:

Site9, Inc.  
329 NE Couch Street, Suite 302  
Portland, OR 97232  
P: 503.248.4440  
E: info@site9.com 
  *[P:]: Phone
  *[E:]: Email
